ZTE
ЗТЕ
zst you I see some kind of imperial
зст вы Вижу какой-то имперец
you have there, this emperor whom the
у вас там этот император которого
Bolsheviks
большевики
shot is cool I’m from the city of
расстреляли прикольно Я из города
Khmelnitsky You’re from the Moscow
Хмельницкий Вы откуда я с Московской
region and I
области а
don’t know the city around here I thought I knew there
возде не знаю я думал там
very negative Yes, but you did
очень негатив Да а вот вы делали
some actions to make Lenin shorter
какие-то акции чтобы Ленина короче
they took me from Red Square Yes, we
забрали с Красной площади Да мы
signed petitions and our guys
подписывали петиции и там наши ребята на
went out to picket there Hooli tol and
пикеты выходили Хули тол
you’re like Now you’re for
при А вы типа Сейчас вы как за
the restoration of the Russian
восстановление Российской
Empire No, that’s no longer possible In any
империи Нет это уже невозможно В любом
case, the imperial ideology is very close to me I
случае очень близка мне идеология
wonder what the imperial
интересно А в чём состоит имперская
ideology consists of I’m not really  strong in imperial
идеология Я не совсем силён в имперских
ideologies I really like the
идеологиях Мне очень нравится как
policy of the empire, which was like the
политика империи которая была как бы и
migration policy at that time and how the
миграционная политика в то время и как
agricultural industry is cool. And who were your
агропромышленность это прикольно А у вас
ancestors under the
предки кем были при
empire? Well, I had a
империи Ну у меня был
grandfather who was a white
дед был белым
Cossack, it would also not be like who? Well  about
казаком бы также не убл Какие кто Ну про
great-grandfathers, usually
прадедов четверо обычно у
people have four, unfortunately I don’t know, unfortunately
людей к сожалению не знаю к сожалению
it’s very expensive It’s all that simple Well, it
это очень дорого Это всё что просто Ну
turns out that for
получается как бы у
the majority of those who belonged to the Empire, the Empire
большинстве кому принадлежала Империя
belonged to the emperor Yes,
Империя принадлежала императору Да все
everyone else there was
остальные там были это как
like his subjects, yes, that is, it turns out
бы подданные его да то есть получается
your ancestors were in this empire  didn’t
ваши предки в этой империи ничего не
mean anything, so it turns out I
значили так получается я к
unfortunately know Well, all the ancestors of all
сожалению зна Ну так все все предки всех
people except if you are not a Descendant of the
людей кроме если у вас вы не Потомок
Tsar, well, in short, your ancestors in the Empire
царя да то короче ваши предки в Империи
didn’t mean anything, yes Well, yes, that is, And
ничего не значили да Ну да да то есть И
you like it
вам это нравится
politics Well, this is in every way better than  Now
политика Ну это всяко лучше чем Сейчас
now you are signing some kind of petition
сейчас вы какую-то петицию подписываете
Yes, petitions
Да петиции подписва ещё
were signed by your
подписывали
ancestors did not have any vote, but you
ши предки не имели никакого голоса ж вы
go to elections here, you
тут на выборы ходите петиции
don’t sign petitions for elections Well,
подписываете не Жу на выборы Ну а
why do you sign petitions, there is an
петиции зачем подписываете есть
emperor, you have this ruler there, he
император у вас там вот это правитель
keeps himself in short Let him
само держится короче Пусть он
decide  you yourself believe your own words
решает сами верите своим словам
decides And who
решает А кто
decides exactly, I don’t know well And who in
решает точно это не зна хорошо А кто в
Russia decides matters Everyone
России решает дела Все
Who specifically
Кто конкретно
Kolomoisky
коломойский
forelock Well no, well, if you look at it like that Yes,
чуба Ну нет ну если так посмотреть Да
it’s clear that Vladimir Vladimirovich is
понятно что Владимир Владимирович чтото
trying to do something You directly called him that
там пытается Ты прямо его назвал так
Vladimir Vladimirovich by his middle name, his
Владимир Владимирович по имени отчеству
roommate retom  I’m careful
сожитель ретом я аккуратненько
about
прово
VN not Well, it’s just easy for you to say You’re
ВН не Ну вам просто легко говорить Вы
probably not from Russia but I’m like I’ll
наверно не из России а мне как бы я сес
say something wrong to me in front of And I
что-нибудь не так скажу ко мне при А я
thought you were an imperial and you’re like for Putin no
думал вы имперец и вы типа за Путине не
I don’t support the cool first
я не поддерживаю прикольно первого
imperial not for Putin  I met and you support the war
имперца не за Путинцев встретил а войну
against Ukraine.
против Украины поддерживаешь
I am against any war, I support my
Я против любой войны я поддерживаю своих
guys. Who is there with whom I grew up? Who
парней Кто там с кем я вместе рос кто
went? That is, you support Yes, the
пошёл То есть ты поддерживаешь Да
occupation of Ukraine No, I don’t. Support the OYU of
оккупацию Украины Нет я не Поддержи ОЮ
Ukraine, just wait. Support me, I
Украины ну подожди Поддержи я я я
help and support my boys who
помогаю и поддерживаю своих пацанов кто
went there.  how did they go on their own, did they
пошёл туда как пошёл они самостоятельно
go here themselves, someone took someone,
пошли тут сам кто-то кого-то забрали
raped them, so wait, I didn’t understand, did
насили Так подожди то и я не понял то
Putin send them, or did they go themselves,
Путин их отправил или они сами ещё пошли
why did they send someone, someone, someone, did
зачем они пошли кого-то кого-то кого-то
Putin send them? So what about those themselves?  posh
Путин отправил Так а те что сами пош
one there is one there is someone who went himself Well, he
один есть один есть кто сам пошёл Ну он
himself went to fight against a Foreign country and
сам пошёл воевать против Чужой страны и
you support him So you support
ты его поддерживаешь Значит ты
this
поддерживаешь эту
war I do not support the killing of
войну я не поддерживаю убийства
the Slavs Yes but your boys Yes they went to
славян Да но твои пацаны Да пошли
kill the Slavs they the Slavs went to kill
убивать славян они славяне пошли убивать
the Slavs It’s their choice For now in short it’s
Славян Это их выбор Пока короче это
Akhmat  strength, in short, there saw it as the son of
Ахмат сила короче там видел это как сын
Akhmat, the son of this
Ахмата сын этого
Kadyrov, beat up a type of Russian and that all
Кадырова избивал типа русского и что все
Russians will swallow the Truth Well, this And
русские глотну Правда Ну вот это И вот
this is very, very pathetic that no one
это очень очень жалко что никто ничего
can do anything
не может делать
instead of, in short, establishing
вместо того чтобы короче наводить
order in their country, they go to die and
порядки в своей стране идут умирать и
kill the Slavs in
убивать славян в
ukra one street would tell me there is
укра один ул сказал мне бы уже такого
no such enthusiasm as at the beginning he will not go to the street again
энтузиазма нет как в начале он ул больше
because what kind of
не поеду потому что какой мы несём
Russian world are we bringing if a
русский мир если в Мариуполе уже
mosque has already been built in Mariupol he says I don’t understand
построили мечеть он говорит я не понимаю
while our guys there are getting migrants
пока парни наши там заводят мигрантов
who
которые
will destroy Russian Russian-speaking even
уничтожат русских русскоязычных даже
Slavs everything is very  it’s difficult and so why do you
славян всё очень сложно и так зачем ты
support these guys? Why should I
поддерживаешь этих пацанов А что мне
go against my guys? I don’t understand what should
против своих парней пойти Я не пойму что
I say, guys, that’s it. Come on, don’t
мне сказать парни всё Идите на мне не
[ __ ] me like that and tell me guys, in short,
бли так и скажи парни короче
turn around, [ __ ] come here. Why the hell should
разворачивайтесь бля идите сюда Нахрена
you kill the Slavs, but they are killing the Slavs, the Slavs are
вам убивать славян но они убивают славян
killing the Slavs, you understand
славяне убивают славян понимаешь
half  half of them can’t
половина половина с не сейчас не может
come now because if they leave they
прийти потому что если они уйдут они
will be deserters and they will be put in prison. And
будут дезертирами и их посадит в тюрьму
in prison they will take one of their dicks away and
А в тюрьме их один хуй заберут [__]
then they will recruit them,
потом завербуют
look, like, you
смотри ну типа ты поддержишь ты
support the murder of
поддерживаешь убийство
the Slavs No, I don’t support the elephant Well,
славян Нет я не поддерживаю слон Ну как
look at your boys  Yes, you send
Смотри ты своим пацанам да присылаешь
some money, goods, and so on.
какие-то деньги товары и так дальше Да
Yes, well, that is, you support, you
да ну то есть ты поддерживаешь ты
arm them so that they kill the Slavs, I
вооружает их чтобы они убивали славян я
don’t
не
arm them, you give them, I convey that
вооружают им даёшь я передаю что матери
their mothers prepared food for them, clothes,
им подготовили еду одежду
no
не
more, any support for the army is
более любая поддержка армии - это
support for the war. I don’t understand.  I’ve been with people
поддержка войны Я не понимаю я с людьми
since birth And what if I should send them
с рождения был И что мне как бы их
this and they ask you Come on, give
это а они просят тебя Дава давай
it all to us Yes, they don’t ask, the
передавай нам это всё Да ня не просят
mothers ask that I’m in touch with the mothers
матери просят что я с матерями на связи
and everyone is very
и все очень
worried. What can I do for my part? I’m a
переживают Я что могу со своей стороны я
hairdresser giving haircuts to wounded guys.
парикмахер стригу парней раненых
hospitals are so
госпиталя так
far away And mothers don’t want to go out and ask
Дале А матери не хотят выйти задать
Putin a question like Putin And why are our
Путину вопрос типа Путин А за что наши
children dying
дети умирают
there I’ll say So for many, this
там я скажу Так что очень у многих этот
question has been brewing for a long time, but everyone’s
вопрос уже давно назревает но у всех
hands are tied, no one can
связаны руки никто не может ничего
do anything because
сделать потому что настолько связала
the system’s hands are so tied, I’m here  Russian nationalist,
система руки я вот русский националист
yes, but I can’t do anything extra, it’s
да а я не могу ничего лишнего
very sad that we are like trash in our
сде очень печально что мы у себя в
country Well, that’s
стране
how it is Well, it’s clear Yes,
как сорная на Ну так и есть Ну понятно
this is all the trash they control us
Да вот эта вся швали они управляют нами
and they achieved this, they started
и они добились этого развязали
a war Yes, but Bose staged the genocide of Russians
войну Да но Боше геноцид русских
Yes, but look  at the same
устроили Да но смотри в тоже в то же
time, an acquaintance of yours who, like, went
время твой знакомый который типа пошёл
to war against Ukraine, he is also a Russian
на войну против Украины он тоже русский
nationalist. As I
националист Я так
understand the war, how many Russian
понимаю войну Сколько русских
nationalists are fighting against Ukraine, they
националистов воюет против Украины
deliberately went to the Donbass, there are
поехали сознательно на Донбасс там
all sorts of Rusichi and SMU Sich, yes, I know. Well, let’s
всякие Русичи и СМУ сичи да чи знаю Ну
go, yes,
поехали
many Russians Well, that’s the idea  it’s the ldnr
да многие русские Ну по идея это лднр
to protect correctly And what’s wrong with the
правильно защитить А что что не так с с
ldnr they were subjected to how many Russian
лднр подвергались сколько там русских
people are there were they were exterminated
людей находится подвергались уничтожения
Well, tell me how Ukraine raska from
Ну расскажи вот мне как Украин раска с
Ukra destroyed the people of
Укра уничтожила людей
the VDN they fired at how many obres because the
вдн обстреливали скоко обре потому что
war began because you led the
война началась потому что вы в году вели
Crimean troops to Donetsk Luhansk in 2011
войска Крым в донецкую луганскую
region This means that it was necessary to bomb
область Это значит что надо было бомбить
houses because the war was on ours, they were shooting at us, they
дома так война была по нашим стреляли
were shooting at us. Well,
наши стреляли Ну
of course, the SPO
конечно не СПО
didn’t shoot anyone there at all, or
всеми никого там вообще не стрелял или
what do you think, for example, that they just
как Как ты думаешь например что просто
drove up Ukraine says let’s go
подъехали Украина говорит давай мы вот
there somewhere in the house Shots Here are the guys with
туда где-то в дом Выстрели Вот ребята с
Kharkov on a tank Well, it’s clear that
Харькова на танке Ну понятно что нет
no, well, it’s the guys’ idea Yes, protect the Russian
нет ну идея парней Да защитить русских
people in the LPR, Novorossi, wait, I
людей в лднр новоросси подожди я
understand correctly that you understand that
правильно понимаю что вы понимаете что
you cannot protect the Russians in Russia,
вы не можете защитить русских в России
yes Kadyrov SN is a [ __ ] dog, the strength of this
да Кадыров СН собаку бля сил этого
crane is [ __ ] just demonstrative,
журавля бля просто показательно
you can’t protect the Russians
выставлял вы не можете защитить русских
people in Russia [ __ ] going to protect
людей в России бля едете защитить
Russian people somewhere in Ukraine I
русских людей где-то в Украине это я
agree This is funny I myself don’t
согласен Это смешно Это я сам этого не
understand this why
понимаю почему
this is just a laugh Well this is me
так это просто ржака Ну это это я
agreeing This is [ __ ] up First you need to
согласен Это [__] сначала надо себя
figure yourself out and then go somewhere else This is
разобраться потом куда-то лезть ми это
not
не
happening to us  huge money everywhere, it’s
происходит нам огромные деньги везде это
us Ordinary people like that can’t, but
мы Обычные такие люди не можем та
ordinary people, it’s in your heads, look, a bunch of
обычные это у вас в головах смотри куча
Russian nationalists went to fight
российских националистов поехали воевать
against Ukraine for some kind of LPR, yes, a
против Украины за какой-то там лднр да
bunch, and your friend, it turns out, is also
Куча и твой вот знакомый получается тоже
deliberately gone And a bunch of them
сознательно Пошёл Да и куча таких потому
because in their brains  it’s not them, but Akhmat that Akhmat
что в мозгах у них не а Ахмат что Ахмат
makes money from this.
на этом набивает
Well, moreover, you saw this
деньги Ну более того ты видел эти
news. Yes, how in the Lugansk region there is
новости Да как в Луганской области
so much rape of
сколько изнасилования
these Russian girls who live in
сде русских этих девушек которые живут в
Lugansk. Yes,
Луганске Да
how much it is very sad, I hate them with
сколько это очень печально я их ненавижу
all
всей
my heart, many
душой многие
guys and what do you understand? Look, you
ребята и что понимаешь Вот смотри ты
you hate, you sing and the boys also
ненавидишь ты поешь и пацаны также
hate, but in short, let’s go damn die
ненавидят но Короче поехали блин умереть
in
в
Ukraine, their choice, they thought that I didn’t
Украину их выбор они посчитали что я не
go,
поехал
I was left alone
полене я остался
T Maybe they need to pick on the brains In short,
Т Может им нужно капать на мозги Короче
boys, let’s solve
пацаны Давайте может решать в России
our problems in Russia, I say one already, one
наши проблемы говорю один уже гово один
already went
уже уехал
back  he didn’t understand that
обратно он не понял что никакого
there is no Russian World, it’s the BC
русского Мира нету это ВС
[ __ ], he came back, the
пизд он вернулся
guys
ребята
put it
вставили
under these
под эти
[ __ ] ones, like
ебучие как
[ __ ], well, they wrote it down, Well, they signed the contract and that’s it And
Бля ну записали Ну контракт подписали да
in the end they are there And now Bully, it’s no
и всё И в итоге они там А сейчас Хули
use, even if deserters are [ __ ] and in
толку-то даже если дезертиры бля а в
prisons they’re already constantly recruiting
тюрмах оху вербуют уже постоянно
stormtroopers are already sending
штурмовиками уже отправляют на
hostages to death in the situation, the majority Yes, I’m
смерть заложни ситуации большинство Да я
sure there are no really normal advances.
уверен никаких продвижений толком
How can you fight if you
нету Как можно воевать если ты сам этого
don’t want it? What results can you achieve with
не хочешь Какие можно достигать
enthusiasm
энтузиазма
and fight in Ukraine to protect
да воевать в Украине защищать там
Russian-speaking people there in Odessa in Donetsk in
русскоязычных в Одессе в Донецке в
Lugansk if you can’t protect them stupidly
Луганске если не может их защитить тупо
in  Moscow in
в Москве в
Moscow Yes, we want, we have been striving
Москве Да у нас Мы хотим мы добиваемся
for how long for a Russian cultural center to be opened for us
уже сколько чтобы нам открыли Русский
in Moscow, there is simply
центр культуры в Москве просто культуры
no culture, there is no Russian cultural center. But the
нету русского центра культуры Зато
Tajik diaspora in the center of Moscow
таджико диаспоре в центре Москвы
has been allocated
выделили
see, look, you understand that something is
сеэ смотрите Вы понимаете что что-то не
wrong and you are still going to fight like meat  to
так и всё равно едете воевать как мясо в
Ukraine Well, that’s what I have, well, I’m not going anywhere
Украину Ну вот это у меня ну я никуда не
Well, those Yes, what’s up,
Ну вот те Да что там
friends Tazhin came back alone now he’s
друзяки тажин вернулся один сейчас он
undergoing rehabilitation now, he lost his
сейчас проходит реабилитацию лишился
leg, a boy younger than me, well, he’s 18 years old,
ноги парнишка младше меня ну 18 лет
but What’s what he says,
ему а вот Что вот что он говорит
for example, who’s to blame for what he has
например кто виноват в том что у него
now there’s no
теперь нет
leg Well, nothing he says
ноги Ну ничего не с что он говорит всё
anyway, then he’ll go anyway, well, he’s already
равно потом поедет всё равно ну его уже
caught up in all this already in the sense that
затянуло это уже всё это в смысле то
is, he lost his leg without understanding why
есть он лишился ноги не понимая за что
he’ll go there And he’ll still go there No, well,
выедет И всё равно поедет туда Да не ну
he has his own attitudes  there is, in any
свои-то у него установки есть в любом
case, in his head he thinks
случае в голове он считает
that wait and you and you don’t try to
что подожди а ты а ты ему не не пробуешь
tell him that hey, why the hell should you go
сказать что слухай А нахрена тебе ехать
yet you [ __ ] already have no leg, in short,
ещё ты [__] уже без ноги короче ради
why are you going there for someone to die for
чего ты туда едешь за кого сдохнуть за
Putin We discussed Yes, he came when
Путина Мы обсуждали Да он приезжал когда
he says  bro I understand all this, but
он говорит братан Я всё это понимаю но
how much time has passed, everyone there
уже сколько времени прошло у меня там
has become like family. I can’t anymore. It’s just
все стали как семья Я не могу уже Просто
elementary to let the guys down there already at
элементарно там парней подвести уже в
the beginning, I should have said all this.
начале надо было это всё говорить
Wait, wait, I don’t understand again, were
Подожди подожди я ещё раз не понимаю то
they forced, were they deceived, or is it all there?
их заставили их обманули всё или это там
they are like a family, these are completely different things
они как семья это совсем разные вещи
if, as a family, he voluntarily, if he
если Как семья он добровольно если он
understands that they are for slaughter, then on the contrary, he
понимает что их на убой то он наоборот
will zigzag as short as he
будет петлять короче как
can, if he understood that of course he
может е бы он понимал что набо конечно
wouldn’t go his own listening, again, I can’t get my head
бы сво слуша опять же в голову не могу
around the room, no one has his own idea  especially, he’s
зале никому своя есть идея особено уже
been fighting there for several years now.
не первый год воюет там
So I don’t want to, damn it’s a sore
Поэтому не хочу бля это больная
point. I just don’t understand at all how this is
тема Просто я вообще не понимаю как это
understood in
понима в
Russia. It’s
России там же
funny, but Russian nationalists
этих Смешно да российских националистов
in Russia are persecuted, imprisoned, in short, they’re killed.
в России преследуют садят короче убивают
Yes, [ __ ], and they shoot down there, you have
Да бля и сбивают там вот у вас
this fighter, this Max Divnich  so he and I are
этот боец этот Макс дивнич так он чтото
moving together with him,
с ним двигаюсь
he was something like he said something against
вместе он что-то типа был Сказал против
there, a mosque somewhere on
там что-то мечеть где-то на озёрах
some lakes, yes We went against it, we recaptured
каких-то да Мы выходили против мы отбили
this place, they wanted to build a huge
это место хотели построить огромную
mosque on the Holy
мечеть на Святом
Lake
озере
there, in general they were there and did not give
там вобще находились там не давали
anything  do thank God they canceled it and
ничего делать слава Богу отменили е и
like all these like Chechen MMA fighters are
типа все эти типа Чеченские бойцы MMA
immediately so against in short di all such
сразу такие против короче ди все такие
cn number one enemy among the Islamic world of
цн номер один враг среди исламского мира
Russia [ __ ] number one but we’re like, well,
России бля номер один но мы как бы вот
we’re together, we have our own unity,
ну мы вот вместе у нас своё единение
look, here’s an interesting question  Do you
есть вот смотри вот интересный вопрос Ты
think Russia should be like
как считаешь Россия должна быть как вот
this Federation with different peoples or
Федерация вот эта с разными народами или
Russia Should remain in Moscow Where
Россия Должна остаться московска Где Вот
Russians historically
там русские исторически
lived there. I think that I think that it is necessary that we
жили Я считаю что я считаю что нужно что
should just send the CIS countries to the
надо нахуй просто страны СНГ слать Ну
[ __ ].
как всё эти средне Азию всех как бы ну
who lived with us differently, wait,
народа которые жили у нас не так подожди
so you have citizens. Okay, we’ll
Так у вас же есть граждане Ладно мы
put the Uzbeks out of the brackets, the Kazakhs
вынесем за скобки там узбеков казахов
there who live in their own countries. But for
там которые живут в своих странах А вот
example, you have the residents of Dagestan,
у вас например жители Дагестана
Tatarstan, Bashkartastan, so they
Татарстана башкартастан Вот они
come, well, no matter what, I think that Well, that’s
приезжают Ну как бы нет Я считаю что Ну
Well  and what’s wrong with them? They haven’t always lived in
Ну а что с ними Они очень всегда жили в
Russia. Well, yes, it turns out, look. Well,
России не Ну да то получается смотри Ну
if they want to build a mosque in
если они хотят построить мечеть в
Moscow. Well, no, I’ll be against it.
Москве Ну нет я буду против этого А
Why against it? Well, look, if it’s a citizen.
почему против Ну смотри если это гражда
And there are their own regions where they can
А свои есть регионы где они могут это
do this. Wait, that is.  look, it’s
делать Подожди то есть смотри вот
interesting that the Russians can
интересно русские могут в Башкортостане
build a church in Bashkortostan Yes, but Bashkor there and
церковь построить Да а башкор там и
others can’t build it in Moscow unless me
другие не могут построить в Москве разве
Well, in the World Cup Yes, well,
ме Ну в ЧМ
first of all, the broadcast is already a monster,
Да ну во-первых в вещать уже до хуище
everything is just a [ __ ] You are a [ __ ] Moskvabat,
всё просто [__] Ты москвабад [__] ну
well, look again no If These are yours
так смотри ещё раз нет Если Это ваши
citizens, yes, that is, I just can’t how it’s
граждане да то есть просто я не могу как
happening in your head at the same time, and
у вас в голове одновременно э делается и
so we want without non-Russians Yes, and we want
вот мы хотим без нерусских Да и мы хотим
an Empire like that there, together with ru with
Империю типа вот там вместе с ру с
other peoples. We want there to
другими народами Хотим мы хотим чтобы не
be no migration of this
было миграция вот этой
incomprehensible
непонятной
Central Asian people,
среднеазиатской народами
as it were.  they don’t give a [ __ ], in principle,
как бы они не выёбываюсь в принципе ну
well, look, if Dagestan, for example,
как вот смотри если Дагестан например
migration from Dagestan to Moscow is going on,
так миграция из Дагестана в Москву идёт
so it’s in the middle of your state, and then that’s what
так это в середине вашего государство да
migrants from
что тобто получается мигрантов из
Dagestan get. Well, not miran, but migrants from
Дагестана Ну не миран а переселенцев из
Dagestan to Moscow are the norm. But for example,
Дагестана в Москвы норм А уже например
from Azerbaijan not  norms yes Well, still
из Азербайджана не норм да Ну всё-таки
more if you look at the historical part, it’s
больше если исторической часть смотреть
like Dagestan is still there and the Tsar
как бы Дагестана всё-таки там да и царе
was like everything. That’s it and
был как бы всё Вот это и
where the [ __ ] was Uzbekistan
а как бы где был бля Узбекистан
Tajikistan in the
Таджикистан в
[ __ ] Kazakhstan Yes, Kazakhstan and
[__] Казахстан Да что Казахстан что
Dagestan approximately In some
Дагестан приблизительно В одни там
periods there Yes
периоды Да
was well, as if there is no speech, the fight is still going now, the
был ну как бы нет реч сеча ещ идт сечас
biggest problem is the
больше самая большая проблема это
migration of the SZI with its indigenous
миграция сзи со своими коренными
peoples,
народами
this is nothing,
это поничем
but in the dance there is a sheep in Moscow Both of
прит в танец там баранец в Москву И те и
them, at about the same time, ended up in the
те приблизительно в одно время попали в
Russian Empire,
Российскую империю
let’s say Well, yes, Well, I’m against it in general  I
допустим Ну да Ну я смою против вообще я
would remove him, [ __ ] me, he's
бы его убрал [__] нахуй меня он вообще
not warm at all I think he's just there, he's
Тепло не холо Я считаю что он просто там
colo I think who Dagestan
он это коло Я считаю кто Дагестан
is bad Yakutia would be left in Russia
нехорошо Якутию оставили бы в России
Yakutia would be left So wait That is, it
Якутию бы оставили Так подожди То есть
turns out you don't like the Dagestanis Well,
получается дагестанцы тебе не нравятся
I can't understand B  what is the logic
Ну вот я не могу понять В чём логику
because everything is connected with crime and
потому что всё связано с преступностью и
connected with influence like about the Yakuts [ __ ]
связано с влиянием как про якутов [__]
Where are they I don’t see them at all even if
Где они их вообще их не вижу даже если
they are there they are very respectful Well I
они есть то они очень уважительно
understand, that is,
относятся б Ну понял то есть ещё раз
look again for example, that is, the Yakuts are Buryats yes
смотри например то есть якуты буряты да
Yeah they are like
Ага они типа
uh  not a fighter, not a fighter, yes, for example, yes,
ээ не борцухи не бойцу да например да
like that And let them be with us like we
типа то А пусть они будут у нас типа мы
will pull resources from their regions and
будем из ихних регионов тянуть ресурсы а
Dagestan we pull resources but damn they
Дагестан мы тянем ресурсы но бляха они
smoke us that they come in large
нас курят что они приезжают в большом
numbers to Moscow and even there they
количестве в Москву да и там порядке
build their own in order, so it
свои строит так
turns out Well  they’re just really
получается Ну они просто очень сильно
[ __ ] up and [ __ ], well, it’s just [ __ ], they’re
уёбываю и Бля ну это просто [__] это
all criminals. Well, as you all say
преступники все Ну как все ты говоришь
now, that all the people are criminals,
сейчас что весь народ преступники навер
so you can say. There
так можно сказать
are also people who are criminals,
Вот там же есть люди которые преступники
and there are those who are normal, just like
а есть которые нормальные также как и
among
среди
Russians, I don’t argue, but they are normal people.  they
русских не спорю да нормальные люди Они
don’t go to Moscow [ __ ] that’s what
не едут в Москву бляд вот для того что
they do here, normal people stay
они делают тут нормальные люди остаются
at home at home there again and Russians
у себя дома у себя там ещё раз а русские
sit only in those cities in which they
сидят только в тех городах в которых они
were born No No probably for the majority of
родились Нет Нет наверно за большинство
the talk Do not Russians travel from different regions
говор Не русские едут из разных регионов
to Moscow or not  they’re coming Well, what about when the
в Москву или нет едут Ну так а что когда
Dagestanis come, what does it
дагестанцы едут что тебя это тогда
make you nervous then if a Russian from Kaluga is traveling
нервничает если русский из Калуги едет
normally and from Vladivostok is normal and from
нормально и с Владивостока нормально а с
Dagestan, damn Well, my
Дагестана бля Ну у меня
enemy is this Well, that is, it
неприятель так это Ну то есть это ты
turns out that you are Well, you have some kind of
получается Ну у тебя есть какие-то там
enemy of a certain Nazi  me and
неприятель определённой наци меня и у
many like-minded people
многих единомышленников
Yes, it’s so good, look it turns out You
Да так хорошо так смотри получается Вы
don’t like some nations there but you want
не любите там какие-то нации но хотите
them to live in Russia I don’t want And
чтобы они жили в России я не хочу А
Yakutia Tatarstan Bashkartastan the
Якутия Татарстан башкартастан тея
question is not right Tatarstan
вопросов нехо Татарстан
Bastan I was recently in Kazan, a wonderful
Бастан я был недавно в Казани прекрасное
place where it’s better there
место там где вот там получше
than in Moscow you can say there isn’t at
чем в Москве можно сказать там нет хотя
least one like that there there are mosques
бы вот такого там там один мечети храмы
Orthodox churches Well, don’t look again at
православные Ну вот не ещё раз смотри то
Tatarstan, you would like it to stay in
Татарстан ты хотел бы чтобы он остался в
Russia Dagestan, I understand you don’t want it, but
России Дагестан я понял ты не хочешь да
Tatarstan actually doesn’t I would
Татарстан на самом деле нет Я бы их
remove them  everything I mean, would you remove them or would you
убрал все В смысле ты бы их убрал или вы
disconnect them, as it were, because it’s good?
отсоединили как бы да потому что хорошо
And for example, if, for example, Russia, as a
А например если например Россия бы как
Russian republic, would be created within the
русская республика бы да создалась в
borders of what regions do you see the
границах каких областей ты видишь
Russian
русскую
Republic?
Республику
Well, listen, I didn’t think about this that Booth would
Ну ну слушай я про это не думал что Бут
just make a Russian Republic  No,
сделать просто русскую Республику Не ну
well, look, if Dagestan
как ну смотри если там Дагестан
separates there, you don’t want their Tatars,
отсоединиться вы не хотите их татары
so you don’t want them, where
отсо их не хотите куда вот где должна
these areas that you
остаться вот те области которые ты
want should remain, for example, well, well,
хочешь например
it won’t be Russia anymore, you know,
ну ну это уже будет не Россия понимаешь
too. If you look at it like that, it’s no longer
тоже Если так посмотреть это уже тоже не
Russia either. Well, then because  look,
Россия Ну тогда потому что смотри вы
if you take an Empire with different peoples,
если берёте Империю с разными народами
then these peoples live in your
да то тогда эти народы живут в вашей
country Yes, and they come to the capital of the
стране Да и они приезжают и в столицу
Empire Yes And you want you want to have
империи Да А вы хотите вы хотите иметь
an Empire with these peoples, suck the juice out of them
Империю с этими народами сосать из них
in the metro to Moscow, but so that they go to
соки в метро в Москву но чтобы они в
Moscow  didn’t come, no, you’re coming, damn
Москву не приезжали да нет вы приезжаете
it, but don’t [ __ ] it, don’t kill
[__] но вы не уёбывайте вы не убивайте
our guys there, don’t download it there for your
там парней наших не качайте там за свой
Islam, it’s like, wait, stop, Islam
Ислам у нас как бы да подожди стоп Ислам
is not their Islam, it’s Russian Islam. Well,
это не их Ислам это российский Ислам Ну
you officially have Russia, yes, you don’t have
у вас официально Россия да у вас нету
what you have  you have the Orthodox religion
что у вас православная религия у вас
and Buddhists live Yes, the Buryats Kalmyks
есть и буддисты живут Да буряты калмыки
Arats Putin said or that not in
араты пути Путин сказал или что не по
fact you have in fact in fact
факту у вас по факту по факту у вас
Russia is not a country of one nation, for example,
Россия не страна одной нации например
like Poland, yes it
как вот там Польша да
is there, the Polish Republic and
это есть там Польская республика да
Russia is absolutely a Federation
Россия - это Федерация абсолютно
different nationalities Yes subject That is, it’s
разных народности Да субъекта То есть
just in your head that I see it
просто в твоей голове вот я смотрю
gets along, you want to simultaneously have
уживается ты хочешь одновременно иметь
Russia within such borders and with these
Россию в таких границах да с этими
peoples and And on the other hand, you are
народами и И тебе с другой стороны тебе
unpleasant about the order of these
неприятны порядки этих
peoples that they are creating this
народов что они творят это
chaos Well, I just can’t understand
беспредел Ну просто не могу понять
why For example, I  I say the same
почему Например я же говорю та же самая
mosque for some reason that you were in Kazan you
мечеть почему то что в ты был в Казани
say there are churches in Kazan Of course there
говоришь в Казани есть церкви Конечно
are of course many churches in Kazan yes yes
есть конечно много церквей в Казани да
then why do
да то почему в
you think it’s normal to have Orthodox churches in Kazan
Казани церкви православной ты считаешь
and when Muslims want
нормально а когда мусульмане хотят
to build a mosque in Moscow you’re the same
мечеть сделать в Москве ты та
[ __ ] well Kazan  in principle, this is a
Бля ну Казань в принципе это
Muslim region And it’s not surprising to you
мусульманский регион Да и тебя не удив
that there is
что там
a church there because Russia was originally an
церк потому что Россия изначально
Orthodox country, that’s why there
православная страна я вот за это при
was Orthodoxy during the empire, in any case,
империи было православие в любом случае
once again, that is, look at Tatarstan
ещё раз ещё раз то есть смотри Татарстан
- this is the place where
- это место где и поконо веков проживали
the Tatars lived for centuries, this is their ethnicity  territory
татары это ихняя этническая территория
Yes, they had their own rules there
Да вот у них там были свои порядки туда
Russia brought churches not so long ago if
Россия принесла церкви не так давно если
we can look, yes Well, they don’t get [ __ ],
можем смотреть да Ну они не выёбываюсь
not so [ __ ] or not [ __ ],
не так выёбывается или не выёбывается
but
это но
look, Russian Can put a church in
смотри русский Может поставить церковь в
Tatarstan And when a Tatar wants a church
Татарстане А когда татарин хочет церковь
in Moscow, it makes you feel  some kind of
в Москве это у тебя вызывает какое-то
amazement Well, in Dagestan, for example, there are a
изумление Ну в Дагестане например очень
lot of people who are against churches, for example, there are
много кто против церквей например
a lot of ours, that’s how many there were
наших очень много вот сколько там
recently, there was a case when
недавно вот случай был когда храм
our temple there was shot by these [ __ ] Dags And
расстреляли наш там эти бля [__] А И
why did they want Well, what do they want? That’s what
почему а хотели Ну причём Вот это хотели
this mosque is an Azerbaijani
то что вот э мечеть это азербай
entrepreneur  I wanted to do this to
предприниматель хотел это сделать
open someone who doesn’t even live in Russia. That
открыть который даже не в России живёт
is, I wanted to open it as if, but not only was there
То есть это хотел открыть как бы а мало
supposed to be a mosque there. There
того что там должна была быть мечеть Там
should have been a huge complex there, there’s a
должно там был там был огромный комплекс
madras mosque there, like there’s a
там мечеть мадраса типа там это
hospital there, a hotel there, there’s a shopping center. I
лечебница гостиница там торговый центр Я
still don’t understand.  Well, let’s say
всё равно не понимаю Ну вот скажем
why. For example,
почему Например
Moscow can, for example, open a church
Москва может например открывать церковь
there in Ukraine in the territory of Russia there
там в Украине в на территории России там
in Chuvashia in Bashkortostan,
в Чувашии в Башкортостане
and when these same people want to open their
а когда эти же народы хотят открыть свою
religious building in Moscow, it’s like
культовое сооружение в Москве это типа
Mosk, and you’re not a native Muscovite. As I
Моск причём Ты же не коренной Москвич Я
understand it, yes, a native Well, how  root, not well,
так понимаю да кореной Ну как кореной не
you said Grandfather, like a Don Cossack Well, yes,
ну ты сказал Дед типа Донской казак Ну
that is, your parents came to Moscow somewhere, for example, they were
приехали в Москву например так
n’t born here Well, your grandparents
не тут родились Ну бабушка с дедушкой
came to Moscow Grandma wasn’t Grandma was
приехали в Москву бабушка не Бабушка
also born here That’s good further about well,
тоже тут родилась Это е дальше хорошо
someone  wasn’t born in Moscow Well, yes,
ну кто-то ж не родился в Москве Ну да
obviously. That is, it
явно То есть
turns out that you came from some region.
получается ты с какого-то региона
Yes, and you can, like,
приехал Да и ты можешь в Москве типа
build a church in Moscow. But for example,
делать церковь да А например
one of these Muslims cannot have
кто-то из этих из мусульман не может
a mosque. They just can. Why can I mean that, for
мечеть Просто может Почему может я к
example, here  we have it on
тому что вот например вот у нас есть на
Buto Yes, this is the district just there,
Буто Да вот это раон просто там ну есть
well, there is a department there in Moscow. There he is a
отде тако Москве Там он вот мусульманин
very influential Muslim trying to open a
очень влиятельный добива чтобы открыть
full-fledged mosque, he has already been there for about
мечеть полноценную он уже там где-то на
5 years, he has been negotiating everything there,
протяжении 5 лет всё там договаривался
buying land, and so on and so
земли покупал и так далее и тому
forth Yes, without  problems but he is and here
подобное Да без проблем но он это а тут
he is [ __ ] Earth first of all This is [ __ ] this
[__] он Земля во-первых Вот это бля это
Holy Lake [ __ ] And why is it holy By the way,
Святое озеро бля А чем оно святое Кстати
I didn’t understand, well, according to the traditions of the church, according to the
я не понял ну там по преданиям церкови
traditions of the church, only I thought there was
по преданиям церкови только я думал там
some kind of church there No, there was a church there
какая-то церковь Нет там была церковь
for real  in reality, it’s just there
по-настоящему настоящему просто там
in every legend,
в каждом предание
just in oh, the cross is
просто во ом крест
huge What do you think, let’s do this
огром Как ты думаешь давай так
in the end How do you think
напоследок Как ты думаешь чем закончится
the war between Russia and
война России с
Ukraine will end? I think it won’t
Украиной Я считаю она не
end just like it won’t end. Well, I think
закончится как не закончится Ну я считаю
that this is a conflict that may subside and
что это конфликт который может утиха а
then it will happen again
потом опять будет
for us  they won’t change
по у нас не сменятся
power like that again. What does
власть так ещё раз Причём тут у нас
our power have to do with it? Well, we’ve changed from Poroshenko
власть Ну у нас вот сменилось Порошенко
to Zelensky, and that too Everything’s
на Зеленского поменял и что ва тоже Всё
not good, wait again, so the war is not because
нехорошо подожди ещё раз так война не
we have power; there’s some kind of
из-за того что у нас власть какая-то
war because you  they attacked us,
война из-за того что вы напали на нас
yes, this is not a dispute Well, what does it
это да это не спор Ну так А причём тут
matter what kind of power we have if
какая разница какая власть у нас если
you, at least, will not be replaced by you Well,
выми как минимум у нас не сменится Ну
that is, ours.
Прим Ну как минимум что вот про такое
ldn firstly not ldnr but
отношение к лдн во-первых не лднр а
Donetsk and Lugansk region of
Донецкой и Луганской области
Ukraine Novorossiya and you are also from the concept of
Украины новороссия а т ты ещё из концепт
Novorossiya not so It’s the same and what is it
новороссии не так Это же а что это
always you think it’s Novorossiya well they
всегда ты считаешь это новороссия ну
lived there the [ __ ] first Who were there
жили там бляд первые Кто там были там
Russian settlers
русские поселенцы
appeared there liberated from and when these
появились там освободили от и когда этих
who the [ __ ] were all of them and settled there,
этих всех [__] кто там был и заселили
why aren’t they there? let’s do it like that. Why then is it
почему там нет давай так А почему тогда
precisely in these regions that Western
вот именно в этих регионах Западная
Ukraine turns out, why then why then are there
Украина почему тогда почему тогда там
so many Russian-speaking people there?
столько вот русскоговорящих людей потому
Because during the Soviet Union, Yes, they brought a
что При Советском Союзе Да на навели
bunch of workers, Yes, to these cities, Yes, villages  in the
рабочих куча Да в эти в города Да сёла в
Lugansk region, even in the Donetsk region,
Луганской области ещё в Донецкой области
they spoke
говорили
Ukrainian, look at photos like the
по-украински посмотри фотографии типа
thirties and
тридцатых годов двадцатых
twenties ROSI [ __ ]
годов РОСИ
Novoros, you have this [ __ ] Novoros, soon the [ __ ]
бля Новорос у вас [__] этот скоро [__]
Chechens from Akhmat will [ __ ]
чеченцы из Ахмата будут вас
[ __ ] you in Moscow, damn you in the ass. In
[__] в Москве Блин в заднице трахать
short, you [ __ ] think you're [ __ ] up for some kind of
Короче ты [__] за наворот какой-то
bloat.
думаешь [__]
I’m for ours in any case, I
Просто я за наших в любом случае я как
kind of said, [ __ ] it, in short, okay, I’m still
бы сказал [__] пох Короче ладно я всё
waiting, look, I’m still waiting for one of the
жду я смотри я всё жду когда кто-то из
Chechens to publicly [ __ ] up some
чеченцев Да публично от пиздят какого-то
Russian nationalist like that in Moscow, you
русского националиста вот так в Москве
know, I want to see how the Russian
знаешь Я я хочу посмотреть как русские
nationalists will be  continue to be silent
националисты Будут дальше молчать потому
because you really are nationalists here. Yes,
что вы реально вот у нас националисты Да
if anything stood up there against Yanukovych
если что встали там против Януковича
against the Armed Forces and the nationalists tolerated you Well, Well, in
против ВС а вас националисты терпил Ну
Ukraine Yes, there is a gay parade for the GBT.
вот Ну вот Украине Да там гей парад гбт
Why don’t yours
Почему ваши ничего не
do anything? You have gay clubs in Moscow.
предпринимают у вас гей-клубы в Москве
you have questions, we
есть есть есть Какие у тебя вопросы есть
don’t at least Wait, you
у нас нет хотя бы Подожди у тебя у тебя
have gay clubs in Moscow
в Москве есть гей-клубы
at the legislative level, it’s
уровне на законодательном уровне
prohibited again Well, you have, you have
запрещено ещё раз Ну у вас есть у вас
a lot of, there are a lot of gay clubs, I don’t know, a lot of Yes, in
куча куча есть гей клубов Я не знаю куча
short, look, in general, okay, we
Да Короче смотри В общем ладно
talked, I talked  I’ll say So, I’ve
поговорили поговорили я скажу Так я вот
always been interested in meeting a Russian
всегда интересно было встретить русского
nationalist to talk to him Yes, I thought
националиста поговорить с ним Да я думал
they were there for Russia, in short, for Russia But really, damn
они там за Русь короче за Русь А реально
Russian nationalists have become
блин русские националисты стали
somehow tolerated like that Yes, in Russia
какими-то терпила такими Да в России
we just [ __ ] we can’t do anything But they
просто Бля мы ничего не можем Но зато
dream of ka
мечтают ка
iri va SRO  Mosk no in short Kato
ири ва СРО Моск нет короче Като
Novoro
Новоро
obli physics about myself
обли физи про для себя
I don’t understand why we haven’t sorted ourselves out, we’re going
пози не понимаю почему мы не разбра себя
somewhere for the sake of the sword Why give everything to the Armed
лезем куда-то для мечу Зачем всё давай
Forces
ВС
well, so we
хороше вот мы
saw it understands that it’s their
увидели понимает вот это что там их
Akhmat, damn it, he’s nice there And they, in short, are going to
Ахмат блин там милит А Они короче идут
fight to die in Ukraine  [ __ ] for
воевать умирать в Украину [__] за
some LDNR LPR badge-fly In short, it’s
какой-то лднр лнр бляха-муха Короче
just
просто
tough, you stupidly can’t figure out the
жесть вы тупо не можете разобраться со с
rights of Russians, stupidly in Russia, yes, you’re
правами русских тупо в России да вы этом
like, in short, slaves [ __ ] Putin
как короче холопы Бля у Путина
Yes, but look how remarkable Yes, that’s
Да но смотрите как примечательно Да вот
who we have watching from different peoples of the
кто у нас смотрит из разных народов
Russian Federation  What is the thinking of
Российской Федерации Какое мышление вот
all these Russian imperials? Yes, they want
этих всех русских имперцев Да они хотят
Tatarstan to be part of Russia.
чтобы Татарстан был в составе России
Yakutia, they want it all to be
Якутия они хотят чтобы это всё было в
part of Russia, so that they control it all,
составе России чтобы они это всё
get resources, but in
контролировали получали ресурсы но чтоб
short, these people came to Moscow
короче Эти люди Приезжали в Москву
for nothing.  They
не Чего это они Блин Из Дагестана лезут
want to build a mosque in Moscow. That is, you
в Москву мечеть хотят строить То есть вы
can there in Sochi, in short, damn it, come
можете там в Сочи короче блин приезжать
to the lands of the Circassians there, and like to the Caucasus
на земли там черкесов да типа на Кавказ
there, and to Dagestan, to all these lands,
там и на дагестанский на все эти земли
you can, yes, as you want, yes, and when they
это можете да вы как хотите да А когда к
come to you, you’re like, [ __ ], what’s this,
вам приезжают вы такие Бля что это там
these guys came in large numbers  Yes, because this, uh, how is it, uh,
Понаехали эти Да потому что этот Ээ как
Russian, Imperial, such a
оно ээ российский Имперский такой
concept, yes, it is built on the hostility of all
концепт да Он построен на неприязни всех
these peoples, they consider the peoples
этих народов они считают народы
to be second-class Yes, and the metropolis of
второсортный Да а метрополия
Moscow, and even Moscow, you see, they don’t
Москва причём даже Москва Видишь не
consider some other regions,
считают какие-то другие области вот у
they have Moscow. This is like Russia for them.
них есть Москва Вот это для них типа
on th Telegram directly at once axis VN
Россия на й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube occupied
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ORV in your ban and even
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
more videos don’t show people immediately don’t
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, for this purpose, Mali has an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
to write directly at once and while there in
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegram okm video sche tezh tsikava and
телеграме окм видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and mi povinni z you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный зв'язок
nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe
подпишись